VADIM CHAIKO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

vadimchaiko@yahoo.com linkedin.com/vadim-chaiko github.com/chkvdm

ABOUT ME

Excited about programming and going to become a professional developer. I have hands-on experience in building projects using node.js, and JavaScript and TypeScript. Basic knowledge of HTML and CSS. Familiar with Python. Love for learning. Ready for new challenges and interesting tasks. Good team communication.

SKILLS

Frontend: HTML, CSS

Backend: JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Python

Framework: Express.js, Jest, Flask

Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Redis

Query language: SQL, GraphQL

Infrastructure: Git

Tools: Visual Studio Code, Docker, Postman API

English: A2+ Russian: native

EXPERIENCE

My Business Card Website

Jul 2023

Frontend developer

My business card website. Based on basic HTML and CSS using the Bootstrap library. The site contains some sections such as: about, my project, certificates and others. You can also view and download resumes in various formats.

DevConnect Apr 2023 - May 2023

Backend Developer

Is a minimalistic social network of developers. It provides a platform for developers to showcase their experience, commercial and sandbox projects. The application offers features for user registration, login, portfolio creation, experience management, feedback exchange, and custom CV generation.

Crypto Sandbox Sep 2022 - Nov 2022

Backend Developer

The sandbox-app that allows a simulation of a crypto wallet using a telegram bot. After registration, the user receives a welcome benefit. The user can see the price of cryptocurrencies, check his balance, buy and sell currencies and also view the list of completed transactions. The six most popular cryptocurrencies are supported.

EDUCATION

EPAM UpSkill / Me

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Backend developer

JavaScript, ES6 and Node.js fundamental. Asynchronous programming, Stream API and EventLoop. NoSQL and SQL databases. Testing and debugging. And also TypeScript basics.

Coursera Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

Backend developer

Fundamental programming. Data structures, networks application, program interfaces and databases. Design and creating applications for data retrieval, processing and visualization.

Belarusian State Technological University Mechanical Engineer

Sep 2009 - Aug 2014